(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-31T17:32:37.825742",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
なななな なななな じゃなくて
Not "na-na-na-na, na-na-na-na,"
にににに にににに じゃなくて
Not "ni-ni-ni-ni, ni-ni-ni-ni,"
ぬぬぬぬ ぬぬぬぬ じゃなくて
Not "nu-nu-nu-nu, nu-nu-nu-nu,"
のののの のののの じゃなくて
Not "no-no-no-no, no-no-no-no,"
うん、ねね！
Yeah, Nene!
ねねねねねねねね！大爆走
Ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne! Super runaway!
はじめようぜ オレンジサンタ 桃鈴ねねです！
Let's start! Orange Santa Momosuzu Nene here!
異世界から来ました アイドル志望の新米VTuber
A rookie VTuber aspiring to be an idol from another world!
まあ とにかく 軽く行きましょう
Well, let's take it easy anyway,
ちょっとくらい 気にししたって スパッて
even if you worry a little, just cut it clean!
うおって感じでさ ぱらっとやっていこう
With a "whoa" feeling, let's do it smoothly,
諦めノヴァルス馬鹿正直だよねーねーねねね
giving up is a waltz, we're stupidly honest, right?
ほんのこともあるけど 悔しいこともあるけど
There are hard times, and frustrating times too,
大丈夫 今日もしっかりお目覚めして
but it's okay, wake up well again today!
いつかはきっと スーパーねねち！
Someday for sure, Super Nenechi!
ついてきて ねねねねねねねね！
Follow along, ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne!
天国で行こうぜ 全開で行こう！
Let's go to the top, let's go full throttle!
思いきりやれば なんとかなるよ
If you do it with all your heart, it'll work out!
ポンコツだっていい ご機嫌だっていい
Clumsy is fine, good mood is fine,
戦い抜いていこうよ ねぇ！
let's push through it, hey!
大爆走！
Super runaway!
野菜ジュースもちゃんとお菓子揃えて準備オッケー！
Vegetable juice and sweets ready, preparation OK!
でもあさも苦手 夜も苦手
Even so, mornings are tough, nights are tough,
やっぱり素直に 生きたいよね！
after all, I want to live honestly!
たくさんの人に愛されあい チュチュチュ チュチュチュ！
Loved by so many people, chu-chu-chu, chu-chu-chu!
大好きなみんなに愛されあい チュチュチュ チュチュチュ！
Loved by everyone I love, chu-chu-chu, chu-chu-chu!
そしたらなるんだ ハイパーねねち！
Then I'll become Hyper Nenechi!
やってちゃってねねねねねねねね！
Let's do it, ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-ne!
天国で行こうぜ 全開で行こう！
Let's go to the top, let's go full throttle!
歌は誰にも負けたくないな 大きな声で！
I don't want to lose to anyone in singing, with a loud voice!
ちょっとトイレ行ってくるね！
I'm going to the bathroom real quick!
レッツゴー！
Let's go!
ねね！
Nene!
よっしゃよっしゃよっしゃよっしゃ！
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go!
ねね！
Nene!
よっしゃよっしゃよっしゃよっしゃ！
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go!
なんかなんかなんかじゃなくて
It's not just any ordinary thing,
にににににににじゃなくて
And it's not 'Nini' either,
ぬぬぬぬぬぬぬじゃなくて
And it's not 'Nunu' either,
のののののののじゃなくて
And it's not 'Nono' either,
ただいま！
I'm back!
最後にねねねねねねねねねねねねねねねねねねねねねねねねねねねねねねねねねねねねねねねねね
With tons and tons of Nenes!
世界中プレイこそ世界中で！
Let's play big, let's go wild!
思いっきりやればなんとかなるよ！
If we just go all out, we can make it work!
閉じ立ていい閉じ立ていい！
Let's close it up, let's lock it in!
戦い抜いてていこうよ！
Let's fight it out tonight!
それではまたねね！
And once again, Nene!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
みんな、こんなねね！
Everyone, thank you so much!
改めまして、ホロライブ5期生、オレンジ担当の桃鈴ねねです。よろしくね！
Thank you for having me! Let's make Momosuzu Nene's 3D live a success!
ふぅー…！ちょっと待って！もう、曲の間、息整えるのって本当に必須なんだ！ふぅー…！
Phew... I can finally catch my breath between songs, that's so important... Whew!
えーというわけで、みなさん、ねね3Dになりましたーー！イェーイ！イェーイ！みんな今日は、#たがぐももすずねね3Dで、いっぱい呟いて！Twitter不具合あるみたいなんだけど、でも！そんな中でもねねのことたくさんトレンド入りさせてください！よろしくお願いします！
So, everyone, we finally made it to 3D! Yay! Today we're doing the "Momosuzu Nene 3D" concert, let's tweet lots and lots!
さあ、もうねねについてなんだけどさ、みんなね、見てこれ！くまモード！イェーイ！見ていて、ガオーガオーガオー！笑
So, about Nene... Look at this! Kuma-mode! Yay! Look at this, gow, gow, gow!
なんとね、くまのバージョンまで作っていただきました！ありがとうございます！みんなありがと、みんなありがと！
We even made a Kuma version, thank you so much! Everyone, thank you so much!
さあ、今日はね、みんなに、普段ね、レッスンしてきた成果を見せるために今ここに立って今すので、えーだんだん次に進んでいきたいと思います！みんなトレンド入り…えーすごい！みんなありがとー！トレンド入りなんだって、みんな！うわ、ねね泣いちゃうよ！みんなありがと！ふぅ、お兄ちゃんたちありがとうございます！はい、みんなありがとうございます！
So today, to show everyone the results of the lessons I've been taking, I'm standing right here right now, so let's move on to the next song!
はい、というわけで、早速次の曲に行きたいと思います！それでは聞いてください、最強パレパレード！
Alright, with that said, I'd love to jump straight into the next song! Please listen to this: "Saikyou Parepareedo"!
今や最強パレパレード つまり最高ハッピーハッピー みんな進撃パレパレード つまり更新ハッピーハッピー
Now is the ultimate parade, meaning the ultimate happy-happy! Everyone's advancing parade, meaning constantly happy-happy!
未来宇宙飛んでよ 何もかもが挫るなら 私たちたちが集まる必然 全部愛してね
Let's shoot for a future beyond the universe! Even if nothing goes right, if we gather together, it'll definitely be alright!
誰も誰も気づかない 不思議秘密集めたら 異次元さえ微笑みなのよ
Even if no one notices, if we gather strange secrets, even dimensions will start to smile!
夢叶えたいと願って 願ったなら それは実に素晴らしく 思い通りフラボア
Even if we can't reach our dreams today, if we wished for it, then it's truly wonderfully just as we hoped!
ミステリー 明日の今日も分かんないだから面白いわ いつでもお人を見送ってたいのよ
Mystery, tomorrow won't wait either, so let's have fun because we can't wait!
どうして落ち込んでるの ばかげたラインじゃない、つまらぬものも野望に道がそぼり
Why are we feeling so down? It's totally not worth worrying about!
今や最強パレパレード つまり最高ハッピーハッピー みんな協力パレパレード
Now is the ultimate parade, meaning the ultimate happy-happy! Everyone's cooperating parade!
もっとあるの、当然よ！
Of course we have more to come!
今や最強・パレパレード つまり最高・ハピハピィ
Now, the ultimate parade, meaning the highest happiness!
みんな前進・パレパレード つまり行進・ハピハピィ
Everyone advancing in the parade, meaning marching in happiness!
未来？！ 宇宙？！ 当然よっ
Future?! Universe?! Naturally!
何かもかもが普通なら 私たちが集まる必然性 台無しね
If everything was normal, the necessity of us gathering would be ruined.
誰方も彼も気付かない 不思議＆秘密集めたら 異次元さえ公園なのよ
Nobody notices, but if you gather mysteries & secrets, even another dimension becomes a park.
SOMEDAY 叶えたいと ONEDAY 願ったなら それは実に素晴らしく 思い通りブラボー！
SOMEDAY if you wished to make it come true, ONEDAY, that is truly wonderful, just as you imagined, bravo!
ミステリック 明日も今日もわからない だから面白いわ
Mysterious, tomorrow and today are unknown, so it's interesting.
いつでもお見通しなんて退屈よ
Always seeing right through things is so boring.
どーして落ち込んでるの 冒険足りないんじゃない？
Why are you feeling down? Aren't you lacking some adventure?
集まろう 野望に満ちたストーリー
Let's gather, a story full of ambition!
いまや最強・パレパレード つまり最高・ハピハピィ
Now, the ultimate parade, meaning the highest happiness!
みんな狂乱・パレパレード 文句あるの？！ 当然よっ
Everyone's frenzy parade, got a complaint?! Naturally!
普通？！ 凡人？！ またねっ ひとりひとり違う違うから
Normal?! Ordinary?! See ya! Because everyone is different!
私たちに関わりたくなくても いいんじゃない
Even if you don't want to get involved with us, that's fine.
おそるおそる近づいて 巻き込まれたなんてね あとから抗議却下するのよ
Approaching timidly and getting dragged in, you'll have your protests rejected later.
SOMETHING 特別には きっと理由があるなら それを探しましょう 弱き知らずのチャレンジ！
SOMETHING If there's a reason for something special, let's search for it, a challenge without knowing weakness!
ライブアライブ！ 人生なんて大いに変えられるのよ
Live alive! Life can be changed greatly.
そうよ向きがね九十五度まわれば違うし なんて考えすぎて憂鬱抱えちゃうのさ やめようよ
That's right, if your orientation turns 95 degrees it's different, thinking too much and holding onto depression, let's stop that.
希望はもっとクレイジー 夢は大胆グレグレート
Hope is even crazier, dreams are boldly great.
たまに妄想ヤバヤバい みんな天才ハレハレイト
Sometimes delusions are super dangerous, everyone's a genius bright-eyed.
踊り決めてもっかい！ ポーズこれよ
Decide on the dance, once more! This is the pose.
SOMEDAY 胸の中で ONEDAY 誓ってみた
SOMEDAY I swore in my heart, ONEDAY.
それは実に素晴らしく 思い通りブラボー！
That is truly wonderful, just as you imagined, bravo!
ミステリック 明日も今日もわからない だから面白いわ
Mysterious, tomorrow and today are unknown, so it's interesting.
いつでもお見通しなんて退屈よ
Always seeing right through things is so boring.
ライブアライブ！ 人生なんて大いに変えられるのよ 集まろう 野望に満ちたストーリー
Live alive! Life can be changed greatly, let's gather, a story full of ambition!
いまや最強・パレパレード つまり最高・ハピハピィ
Now, the ultimate parade, meaning the highest happiness!
みんな狂乱・パレパレード 文句あるの？！ 当然よっ
Everyone's frenzy parade, got a complaint?! Naturally!
夢は大胆グレグレート たまに妄想ヤバヤバい みんな天才ハレハレイト
Dreams are boldly great, sometimes delusions are super dangerous, everyone's a genius bright-eyed.
踊り決めてもっかい！
Decide on the dance, once more!
いまや最強・パレパレード つまり最高・ハピハピィ
Now, the ultimate parade, meaning the highest happiness!
みんな狂乱・パレパレード 文句あるの？！ 当然よっ
Everyone's frenzy parade, got a complaint?! Naturally!
夢は大胆グレグレート たまに妄想ヤバヤバい みんな天才ハレハレイト
Dreams are boldly great, sometimes delusions are super dangerous, everyone's a genius bright-eyed.
踊り決めてもっかい！ ポーズこれよ
Decide on the dance, once more! This is the pose.
今野菜強パレパレード つまり最高ハピハピィ
Now, the ultimate parade, meaning the highest happiness!
みんな狂乱パレパレード 文句あるの当然よ
Everyone's frenzy parade, got a complaint? Naturally!
希望はもうブレレイジー 夢は大胆グレグレート
Hope is even crazier, dreams are boldly great.
たまにもそうやばやばい みんな天才はればれーと
Sometimes delusions are super dangerous, everyone's a genius bright-eyed.
踊りきめても一回！ ポーズこれよ
Decide on the dance, once more! This is the pose.
夢は大胆グレグレート たまに妄想ヤバヤバい
Dreams are boldly great, sometimes delusions are super dangerous,
みんな天才ハレハレイト
everyone's a genius bright-eyed.
踊り決めてもっかい！
Decide on the dance, once more!
おどりきめても一回！
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
最強パレパレード、お聴きいただきましたー！どうだったでしょうかー？
That was "Saikyou Parepareedo"! How was it?
実はこの曲ね、あの、3Dが決定する前に、あの、それが発表される前に、メン限の方でね、この曲やるんだけど、今の練習状況としてはこんな感じっていうのをね、あの、みんなに放送でお伝えしてたんだったんだよね。
Actually, before this song's 3D was decided, before that was announced, on member streams, I was telling everyone how my practice was going.
もうそのときはね、とてーも人に魅せられるようなもんじゃなかったんだけど、
Back then, it wasn't something fit to show people at all,
なんとか、なんとかかんとかここまで、なんだかんだなりました！みんなありがとう。
but somehow or other, we managed to get this far! Thank you everyone.
ちょっとお水失礼します。
Excuse me while I have some water.
さてさてさてさてみんな、どう？このステージ、これね、お昼のステージなのー！すごいでしょう？
Now, everyone, how is this stage? This, you know, is a daytime stage! Isn't it amazing?
もうめっちゃねね要素いっぱいのステージを作ってもらいました！遊園地なの！スーパーネネチステージ！イェーイ！
They made a stage packed with Nene elements for me! It's an amusement park! Super Nenechi Stage! Yay!
ほらね、あのね、客席にね、根っこのみんながいるんだよね。ほら見て！すごいみんなあの、同じ動きでペンライトを振ってくれてる！
Look, in the audience, all the Neko-tachi are there. Look! Everyone is waving penlights with the exact same movement!
みんなコメントのみんな、ここにいるんだ今日も。
Everyone in the chat is here today too.
えっとね、今日はそのステージにいるね、みんなの中からこうね、何人か、ねねのステージ上に上がってきてもらいたいと思いますので、
Um, today, from everyone on that stage, I'd like to have a few people come up onto Nene's stage,
それでは、え、ねっこのみんな、どうぞステージへ！どうぞステージへ！
so, um, Neko-tachi, please come to the stage! Please come to the stage!
どうぞステージへ！
Please come to the stage!
にょいん、にょいんってでてきた。
They came out boinging and boinging.
ねえ、見て、スカートの中見ないで！あ、見てって言っても間違えたわ。スカートの中見ないでね、みんな！
Hey, look, don't look inside my skirt! Ah, even if I said look, I messed up. Don't look inside my skirt, everyone!
やだ、見ないで！ねっこのみんなね、なんとね、これ見て見て！普段ね、オレンジ色のね、ニンジンの子だけなんだけど、
No, don't look! Neko-tachi, look at this! Normally, it's only the orange carrot kids,
これ、なんとね、ダイコンのこと、ゴボウの子も一緒に作ってもらいました！ありがとう！素晴らしい、ありがとう！
but this time, amazingly, they made radish kids and burdock kids along with them too! Thank you! Wonderful, thank you!
なんとね、このね、ねっこのみんなね、あ、ねほら見て見て、これほら、地面に埋もれてる子たちいるでしょ、これ。
And you know, these Neko-tachi, look, there are kids buried in the ground, right?
こんな子たちもちょっと持ってみたいと思います。ほっ！よっ！
I'd like to try holding kids like this too. Hup! Yo!
この、ねねのライブどうだった？まだね二曲目なんだけどさ、
How was this Nene live? It's still only the second song, but
もうねね足びちゃびちゃなんだもん、今。え、よかったって？
my feet are already all soaked right now. Eh, it was good?
あ、そっか、そっか、よかった？え、もう、すごいおどりくるいない、くらい、こう、嬉しい気持ち
Ah, is that so, it was good? I'm so happy I could dance like crazy,
今日でハッピーでいっぱいだって。
Today is full of happiness!
じゃあ、
So,
踊り狂ってもらおう。はい、どうぞ。
let's have you dance like crazy. Here you go.
ああ、いいね。
Ah, nice.
もう1回、もう1回ちょっと踊り狂ってもらうわ。ちょっとうまく映るのかった。行きます。
Once more, let's have you dance like crazy again. Let's see if it films well. Here we go.
ほら、踊り狂えよ。
Look, dance like crazy!
うん。いい感じ、いい感じなー。
Yeah. Looking good, looking good!
えっとえっと、じゃあ次は、この子！
Um um, so next is this child!
ででーん、ごぼうの子！ねねのライブはどうだった？
Ta-da, the burdock child! How was Nene's live?
最高だって？ありがとうね、ねえちゃん。俺たちにアイドルという夢をさせてくれてありがとう。
"It was the best"? Thank you, big sis. Thank you for giving us the dream of being idols.
え、どういたしまして。おりこだなが本当に、よくできた子だ。
Oh, you're welcome. Such a good boy, really, such a well-made child.
そして最後は、 よいしょー！
And last is... heave-ho!
これ、いつものみんな、今日新しいオープニングで瓶詰めされてたでしょ、みんな。これいつものみんななの。
This is everyone's usual... Today you were bottled up in the new opening, weren't you? This is everyone's usual.
この子ね、
This child, you see,
1人でぷらんぷらんする。1人でぷらんぷらんするんだ、この子は。おいしょ。
dangles all alone. Dangles all alone, this child. Heave-ho.
ね、かわいいね。かわいくくっつけてもらっちゃって、みんな。よいしょ、よいしょ。
Look, isn't it cute? Having it attached so cutely, everyone. Heave-ho, heave-ho.
えじゃあ、ここでね、ちょっとね、ねねの全身をね、見てほしいので、はい、猫のみんな、猫のみんなパンツ見えちゃうから、ほら、
So here, you know, I want you to see Nene's whole body, so, hey cat everyone, cat everyone, your panties will show, look,
客席戻りなさいみんな、ほら。戻って戻って、みんな、はい。
go back to your seats everyone, look. Go back, go back, everyone, yes.
じゃあ、すごい一気に消えるじゃん、みんな！
Wow, you guys all disappear in an instant!
はい、というわけで、じゃあちょっとねの全身をね、
Right, so then let's look at Nene's whole body,
こう、ゆっくり、
um, slowly,
ゆっくり見てもらおうと思います。はい、カメラマンさんお願いします。
slowly have you look at it. Yes, cameraman-san, please.
おおー……
Ooh...
ああ、どう、どう？あ、ラミィ、ほら、はい。
Ah, how is it, how is it? Ah, Lamy, look, yes.
ラミィ？
Lamy?
ラミィこれ、どう？どうみんな、かわいい？
Lamy this, how is it? How is it everyone, cute?
助かるって？みんな。ありがとう。
"It saves us"? Everyone. Thank you.
はい、はい、はい、かわいい。あー、いいじゃん、いいじゃん！
Yes, yes, yes, cute. Ah, nice, nice!
ありがとう！みんなすごいコメント爆速、助かる！ありがとう。
Thank you! Everyone's comments are super fast, it helps! Thank you.
どう？こんなねーとか、こんなねーとか、いいんじゃないの？あー、とってもいい感じだね！
How's this? Like this nee~ or like this nee~, isn't it good? Ah, it's a very good feeling!
よーし、じゃあ、ここでね、ねねも乗り乗りになったところで、次の曲を聞いてもらおうかな。
Alright then, now that Nene is all pumped up here, I'll have you listen to the next song.
次はね、この遊園地のね、お隣に桃の木がね、すっごいいっぱい咲いてるらしくて、そっちに移って移動、えーと、歌をまた歌っていきたいと思いますので、
Next, I heard that right next to this amusement park, peach trees are blooming in huge numbers, and moving over there, um, I'd like to sing songs again,
それではみんな、昼の部、ここまで！
so everyone, the daytime session, up to here!
恋☆カナ？ピンときたら
Is it love? When it clicks,
say「恋叶え！」って
say "Make my love come true!"
直線的な行ったり来たりだって 止まらないで いて
We're going straight back and forth all over the place, but don't stop
いつか☆を描いて 君へ 届けたい
Someday drawing a star, I want to reach you
一緒に居れるところか 夢オチの3連覇
Far from being able to be together, it's a dream-ending hat-trick
届きそうに見せるのが イマドキの運命？
Looking almost within reach — is that today's destiny?
甘い モノ ほど 染みる 胸 の スキマ に 君 の くれ た 笑顔
The smile you gave me slips into my heart and touches it as much as any sweet could
まだ途中だけど
We're still on our way, but
ありがとう
thank you!
恋カナ？ ピンときたら
Is this love? When you suddenly know,
セイ「恋叶え！」って
say "Make my love come true!"
直線的な行ったり来たりだって 止まらないでいて
Don't stop this direct going-back-and-forth.
決定的なハッピーの予感 もう すぐそこまで
A definite happy premonition is right around the corner.
願 い見切り発射で
I make a snap decision and wish
恋カナ！ ピンときたよ
Is this love! I suddenly knew,
この恋叶うって
that this love will come true.
かき氷の彼女さえ 見つからずにため息
Even shaved ice girls sigh without being noticed,
なんて姿を見せたって いいことないよね
showing a figure like that won't bring anything good.
ドラマチックだと思われても それぞれどこまでもよろしくね
Even if people think it's dramatic, let's get along everywhere.
それぞれどこじゃないゲームだけど どこまでもよろしくね
It's not a game where everyone's equal, but let's get along anywhere.
よろしくね
Nice to meet you.
恋カナ！ ピンときたきゅんでいたい この恋からだって
Is this love! I want to feel a sudden heartbeat, even from this love.
絶妙的なすれ違いなんて 気にしないで
Don't worry about exquisite misunderstandings.
もっと強く光るよ 胸の一番星
It shines even stronger, the brightest star in my chest.
雨の朝も笑ってみせて 星空をきたいで
Smile even on rainy mornings, and look forward to the starry sky.
きらきら レボリューション なんかおこせない
Sparkle Revolution... can't cause something like that.
レボリューション なんかおこせない
Can't cause a revolution like that.
恋カナ！ ピンときたよ
Is this love! I suddenly knew,
この恋叶うって 決定的なハッピーの予感
this love will come true, with a definite happy premonition
もうすぐそこまで 願い見切り発射で
right around the corner, making a snap decision and wishing.
キラリ流れ星 恋カナ！ ピンときたよ
A shining shooting star! Is this love! I suddenly knew,
この恋叶うって 直線的な行ったり来たりだって
this love will come true, with direct going-back-and-forth.
迷わないで いつか星になりたい 君と二つ星
Don't get lost. One day I want to become a star, a double star with you.
ありがとうございましたーー！
Thank you very much!
え、ただいまの曲は「恋☆カナ」という曲をお聞きして、え、いただきましたー！
Um, the song you just heard was "Koi Kana"!
え、みんなに聞いていただきましたー！ありがとうございます！ 恋カナのね、もうね、ねねがね、もうすっごいすっごいすっごいすっごいあこがれてるアイドルのね、きらりんレボリューションの月島きらりちゃんのね代表曲を歌わせていただきましたー！
Everyone listened to it! Thank you! It's Nene's ultimate idol song, the representative song of Kirarin Revolution's Tsukishima Kirari!
どうだった？この曲すっごい難しいの。
How was it? This song is super difficult.
でさ、え、あの、場所を移動してきて夕方のステージに来たんだけどさ、すごい、あの、エモティックでしょ？ えもうエモティックティックでしょ？
And you know, we moved locations to an evening stage. It's super, um, emotional, right? So emotional!
今ねとっても元気な曲をね聴いてもらったんだけど、次はこの背景に合うようなすごいエモ目にみんなに聴いてもらおうかなと思って。
Just now you listened to a very cheerful song, and next I thought I'd have you listen to something super emotional that fits this background.
ただね、のね、息切れがちょっと治まんないからエモさ、エモさよりも、なんていうか、とっても、あの、息切れの方が出ちゃうかもしれないけど。
But you know, my breath hasn't quite settled down, so maybe my breathlessness will show more than the emotion,
聴いてもらおう。ちょっと休憩もしちゃおう。 よいしょ、すごくない？
but please listen. Let's take a little break. Wow, isn't it amazing?
さあ、というわけで次の曲に行きましょうか、みんな！ このね、のまのきがはらほらとまう綺麗なの中でねねは1曲歌いたいと思います。それでは聴いてください、「ガーネット」。
Well then, shall we move on to the next song, everyone? In this beautiful setting where cherry blossoms flutter, Nene would like to sing one song. Please listen, "Garnet".
グラウンド駆け抜くあなたの背中は 空に浮かんだ雲よりも自由で
Your back as you ran across the grounds was freer than the clouds floating in the sky.
ノートに並んだ四角い文字さえ すべてを照らす光に見えた
Even the square characters lined up in my notebook seemed to be a light illuminating everything.
好きという気持ちが分からなくて 二度とは戻らないこの時間が その意味をあたしに教えてくれた
Not understanding the feeling called "I like you," this time that will never return taught me its meaning.
あなたと過ごした日々に この胸に焼き付けよう 思い出さなくても大丈夫なように
Let's burn the days spent with you into this chest, so that it'll be okay even if I don't remember.
あなたと過ごした日々を この胸に焼き付けよう
Let's burn the days we spent together into our hearts,
思い出せなくても 大丈夫なように
So that even if we can't remember, it'll be alright.
いつか他の誰かを 好きになったとしても
Even if one day I fall in love with someone else,
あなたはずっと 特別で 大切で
You will always be special, and dear to me,
またこの季節が めぐってくる
And this season will come around once again.
初めて二人で 話した放課後
After school, when we first talked just the two of us,
誰もしらない笑顔 探していた
I was searching for a smile nobody else knew.
遠くであなたの はしゃいでる声に
From afar, hearing your playful voice,
なぜだか胸が 痛くなったの
For some reason, my heart started to ache.
変わっていくことを 恐がってたの
I was afraid of things changing.
ずっと友達のままで いれる気がした
I felt like we could stay friends forever.
終わっていくものなど ないと思った
I thought nothing would ever come to an end.
果てしない時間の中で あなたと出会えたことが
Being able to meet you in this endless time
何よりも私を 強くしてくれたね
Made me stronger than anything else.
夢中でかける明日に 辿り着いたとしても
Even if I reach tomorrow running in a frenzy,
あなたはずっと 特別で 大切で
You will always be special, and dear to me,
またこの季節が やってくる
And this season will come around once again.
いつまでも忘れないと あなたが言ってくれた夏
The summer when you told me you'd never forget it,
時が流れ 今頃私は 涙がこぼれてきた
Time has passed, and by now, tears have started to spill.
あなたと過ごした日々を この胸に焼き付けよう
Let's burn the days we spent together into our hearts,
思い出せなくても 大丈夫なように
So that even if we can't remember, it'll be alright.
いつか他の誰かを 好きになったとしても
Even if one day I fall in love with someone else,
あなたはずっと 特別で 大切で
You will always be special, and dear to me,
あなたと過ごした日々を この胸に焼き付けよう
Let's burn the days we spent together into our hearts,
思い出せなくても 大丈夫なように
So that even if we can't remember, it'll be alright.
いつか他の誰かを 好きになったとしても
Even if one day I fall in love with someone else,
あなたはずっと 特別で 大切で
You will always be special, and dear to me,
またこの季節が めぐってくる
And this season will come around once again.
ありがとうございました！ガーネットをお聞きいただきました。
Thank you very much! You've listened to "Garnet."
さあ、どうだったでしょうか。途中なんか、
Now then, how was it? In the middle, like,
なんかぐるぐるしてるって皆がよくね、気になっちゃって気になっちゃってしようがなかったけど、
everyone kept saying I was spinning around, and I couldn't help but worry about it,
なんとか、なんとか耐えてる？なんか耐えてる！あ、よかったよかってよかった。
but somehow... somehow I managed? I managed! Ah, good, I'm glad, I'm glad.
ふー、危な危な！
Whew, that was close!
ありがとうねみんな。みんなのあれじゃない、コメントがすごいあの熱意を持ってるから、
Thank you everyone. Isn't it because everyone's comments have so much enthusiasm,
YouTubeとかがちょっと恥ずかしくなっちゃったんじゃないのみんな。ありがとね！
that YouTube or whatever got a bit embarrassing for you all? Thank you!
さてさて、夕方のステージだったんだけどね、今日は昼の部…
Now then, it was the evening stage today, but during the daytime...
Wow Wow 飛び立てば正実!
Wow Wow, if you take flight, it's correct!
どこまでもまだ 高い壁
No matter how far, high walls remain,
ただ怖がってない?
aren't you just scared?
あの空はこんなにも こんなにも 青く澄んでいるのに
Even though that sky is so, so blue and clear,
迷う必要はない ない
there's no need to hesitate. No.
幼いこの足が
These childish feet
踏み出す地と待ってる
are waiting for the ground to step on.
僕ら Flyer! Flyer!
We are Flyers! Flyers!
憧れだけじゃなくて乗り越えて
Surpassing more than just admiration,
キミも Flyer! Flyer!
You are also Flyers! Flyers!
描き出すんだ セカイを
painting out the world!
あの日夢見た夢が 最高の上下気流
The dream we dreamed that day is the ultimate updraft!
何回だって この心 believe in it
No matter how many times, believe in this heart!
明日もきっと快晴!
Tomorrow will surely be clear skies!
Wow Wow 飛び立てば 正解!
Wow Wow, if you take flight, it's correct!
挫けそうになっていた あの日の僕の表情
The expression of me on that day, looking like I might break down,
多分さ boomy boomy
was probably boomy boomy,
弾けそうになっているんだ
looking like it's about to burst.
素直な僕の想いは bloomy bloomy
My honest feelings are bloomy bloomy,
声を飛ばして
letting my voice soar high!
この世に生の意味を持った意味?
The meaning of having life in this world?
そんなこと考えている前に
Before thinking about things like that,
足掻いてみてわ
try struggling,
一歩踏み出して
and take a step forward!
僕ら Flyer! Flyer!
We are Flyers! Flyers!
後悔を怖がってちゃ始まらない
Nothing starts if you're afraid of regret!
キミも Flyer! Flyer!
You are also Flyers! Flyers!
信じてるんだ セカイを
believing in the world!
あの日夢見た夢が 最強の上下気流
The dream we dreamed that day is the strongest updraft!
この心(おもい) believe in it
Believe in this feeling!
明後日も快晴!
The day after tomorrow will also be clear skies!
(Wow Wow)
生み出して 今 ここに僕たちのステージ
Creating it now, here is our stage!
明日は快晴!
Tomorrow will be clear skies!
Flyer! Flyer!
Flyers! Flyers!
響けキミのコールよ
Resound, your call!
3, 2, 1 Say!
Flyer! Flyer!
Flyers! Flyers!
曝け出すんだ セカイを
Lay bare the world!
あの日夢見た夢が 最強の上下気流
The dream we dreamed that day is the strongest updraft!
この想い believe in it
Believe in this feeling!
明後日も快晴!
The day after tomorrow will also be clear skies!
雲突き抜け 描き出す セカイへ
Piercing through the clouds, to the world we paint!
Wow Wow 飛び立てば 正解!
Wow Wow, if you take flight, it's correct!
ちょっとだけちょうだい
Give me just a little bit,
ねえ ひとつだけちょうだいなんて
hey, saying "give me just one more"
あまりにもおねだりしすぎじゃないの
isn't that begging a bit too much?
飽きちゃったらいらない
If you get tired of it, you don't want it,
残しちゃったらごめんなさいって
and saying "sorry if I left some" —
キミのせいかしらね
is that your fault?
ちょっとだけちょうだい
Give me just a little bit,
もうひとつだけちょうだいなんて
saying "give me just one more" again,
甘え上手で罪人じゃないの
aren't you a skilled coaxer and a sinner?
ちょっとだけちょうだい
Give me just a little bit,
全部ちょうだいなんて
saying "give me everything" —
キミのせいかしら 私のせいかしら
is it your fault, or is it my fault?
それちょっとだけちょうだい
Give me just a little bit of that,
ねえひとつだけちょうだいなんて
hey, saying "give me just one more",
あまりにもおねだりしすぎじゃないの
isn't that begging a bit too much?
飽きちゃったらいらない
If you get tired of it, you don't want it,
残しちゃったらごめんなさいって
and saying "sorry if I left some" —
キミのせいかしらね
is that your fault?
限られた時間の中で どれだけのコトが出来るのだろう
In this limited time, how much can we actually do?
言葉にならないほどの想いを どれだけアナタに伝えられるのだろう
How much of these feelings, too deep for words, can I convey to you?
ずっと閉じ込めてた 胸の痛みを消してくれた
You washed away the pain in my heart that I kept locked away for so long.
言い表せない ほどの想いを
Words cannot express how much I feel,
どれだけあなたに 伝えられるだろう
how much of it can I convey to you?
ずっと閉じ込めてた 胸の痛みを 消してくれた
You erased the pain in my chest that I'd kept locked away.
今私が 笑えるのは 一緒に泣いてくれた 君がいたから
The reason I can smile now is because you were there to cry with me.
ひとりじゃないから 君が私を守るから
I am not alone, because you protect me.
強くなれる もう何も怖くないよ 時がなだめてく
So I can grow strong. I'm no longer afraid. Time will soothe
痛みとともに 流れてく
and flow away along with the pain.
昨日の光が 優しく照らしてくれる
Yesterday's light gently shines upon me.
説明すること 無理して笑うこと もしなくていいから
You don't have to explain or force yourself to smile.
何かあるなら いつでも頼って欲しい 疲れたときは 甘えてから
If something's wrong, rely on me anytime. When you're tired, lean on me.
どんなに強がっても ため息くらい する時もある
No matter how strong you try to be, there are times when you sigh.
孤独じゃおもいと 扉を
When you feel lonely, open the door.
共に立ち上がれば また動き始める
If we stand up together, things will start moving again.
ひとりじゃないから 私が君を守るから あなたの笑う 顔が見たいと思うから
Because I'm not alone, because I protect you, because I want to see your smiling face.
時がなだめてく 痛みとともに 流れてく
Time will soothe and flow away along with the pain.
昨日の光が 優しく照らしてくれる
Yesterday's light gently shines upon me.
時に人は 傷つき傷つけながら
Sometimes people hurt and get hurt.
それぞれの違うけど 自分だけの 一人つくりながら 生きてくのだから
Though each place is different, building our own unique life as we live on...
ずっと 諦めないで
Always, never give up.
ひとりじゃないから 私が君を守るから あなたの笑う 顔が見たいと思うから
Because I'm not alone, because I protect you, because I want to see your smiling face.
時がなだめてく 痛みとともに 流れてく
Time will soothe and flow away along with the pain.
昨日の光が 優しく照らしてくれる
Yesterday's light gently shines upon me.
ありがとうございました！ えー、ふうと1曲をお聞きいただきました！ イエーイ！
Thank you very much! You've listened to "Foo" and one song! Yay!
じゃあ ちょっとお水飲ませてください ありがとうございます
Now then, please let me drink some water. Thank you very much.
お、ちょっと夜、夜に水飲むのもなかなか重いな。うん。
Oh, drinking water at night, at night like this, is kind of heavy. Yeah.
よし、さて、あのクマのねねっちじゃなくなったところで、ちょっとね、もう一回ちょっとみんなにスクショ撮ってもらいたくて
Alright, now that we're no longer Bear Nenechi, I'd like everyone to take a screenshot once again.
お写真いっぱい撮ってね、みんな！おいしょー！
Take lots of photos, everyone! Heave-ho!
どれ、どういう感じがみんな好み？うん。
Let's see, what kind of vibe do you all like? Yeah.
いいね、みんなコメントにさ、リクエストさ、してくれない?
Hey everyone, in the comments, won't you make requests?
こういうのとかさ? あ、こういうのとかさ?
Like this kind of thing? Ah, like this kind of thing?
おお、いいじゃん。お強そうだな。
Oh, nice. Looks strong.
お、いいね。ピース?
Oh, nice. Peace?
あ、いいじゃん。いい、いいじゃん、いいじゃん。
Ah, nice. Good, good, that's good!
かわいいポーズしてって?
"Strike a cute pose," you say?
かわいいポーズってなんだ?
What is a "cute pose"?
あ、お、よ、あ、いいじゃん、
Ah, oh, yo, ah, nice,
ローアングルめちゃくちゃいいじゃん。
the low angle is super good!
おお、いい、ローアングルめちゃくちゃいいの。
Oh, nice, the low angle is super good.
あ、いいじゃん。ねねねねねねでやってたポーズ。
Ah, nice. The pose Nene was doing.
え、なんだろう? これ?
Eh, I wonder what this is? This?
おっきい! おサルさんみたいなポーズとか。
Big! Like a monkey pose or something.
これとか。これすごいあれねねお気に入りなんだ。
Or this. This is one of Nene's favorites.
シャキーン! ああ、いいじゃん、いいじゃん。
Shing! Ah, nice, nice.
あのさ、ちょっとさ、アップでさ、アップでさ、
Hey, in close-up, in close-up,
あのキラキラのおめめのうちに返るからさ、ちょっとみんな見てて。いくよ?
I'll turn back into sparkling-eyed Nene, so everyone watch. Ready?
キラキラおめめ、んっ、はっ!
Sparkling-eyed Nene... Hmph, ha!
え、どう? みんな? いい感じ?
Eh, how is it, everyone? Good vibe?
イェーイ! イェイイェイイェイイェイ!
Yay! Yay yay yay yay!
あ、いいじゃん! あ、いいじゃん!
Ah, nice! Ah, nice!
ありがとう! 撮った? みんな撮ってくれた?
Thank you! Did you take it? Did everyone take a picture?
え、いい感じ?
Eh, good vibe?
え、いい、ちょっと、もうちょっと、なんか
Eh, good, wait, a bit more, something...
なんかいいアングルないかな? みんなちょっと写って、撮ってさ、
I wonder if there's a good angle? Everyone, show up and take pictures,
あの、ツイートしてて、ねねもらうね後から。
and tweet them, I'll check them later.
あ、この後ろのさ、背景と入る感じ、おお、めちゃいいな。あ、いいだね。
Ah, this feeling with the background behind, oh, super nice. Ah, that's nice.
みんなめちゃいいじゃん! え、ちょっとこ、こっちからさ
Everyone is super good! Eh, wait, from here...
なんたろうな、ステージ全体をこう
I wonder what, the whole stage like this...
映す感じの、あ、いい!
A feeling of capturing... Ah, nice!
おお、お、おお、めちゃくちゃない? めっちゃいい。
Oh, oh, oh, isn't it crazy? Super good.
みんな、ねねだよ!
Everyone, it's Nene!
ああ、めちゃ良くない、これ? いい? ウィンクして? ウィンク? ウィンクか。
Ah, isn't this super good? Good? Wink? Wink? Wink, huh.
よし、いくぞ。ふっ! ふっ!
Alright, here we go. Hup! Hup!
いい? いい? いい? いい?
Good? Good? Good? Good?
いい? えー、いいじゃーん!
Good? Ee, niiice!
あとは、ちょっと待ってよ。
And then, wait a second.
カメラマンさんが忙しくて大変そうって? 大変ですか?
"The cameraman looks busy and seems to have a hard time"? Is it hard?
全々って言ってたよ、今みんな。
"Not at all," everyone just said.
一番! あ、いい。
Number one! Ah, nice.
これ、いい。あ、これ後ろ姿でさ、客席でさ、欲しいな。
This is nice. Ah, from behind like this, in the seats, I'd love that.
あ、やった!
Ah, yay!
あ、いくない? あ、めちゃ良くない? めっちゃ良くない?
Ah, isn't it nice? Ah, isn't it super nice? Super nice?
あ、みんなこれ、ライブでよくあるやつじゃん。写真撮ろう、みんな写真!
Ah, everyone, this is that common thing at live shows. Let's take a photo, everyone, a photo!
ちょっとしゃがんだ感じです?
Crouching down a bit?
はっ! あ、ライブっぽい!
Ha! Ah, feels like a live concert!
ライブっぽい! みんな場所もちょっと撮って、場所もさ。
Feels like a live! Everyone take some spots, too.
はい! はい、もう1回、ターン。はい!
Yes! Yes, once more, turn. Yes!
はい! はい! はい!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
え、めっっちゃめっっちゃいい! え、待って! え、これ、いいの? え、めっちゃめちゃいいじゃん、ちょっと、めっちゃいいの撮れた!
Eh, suuuper super good! Eh, wait! Eh, is this good? Eh, it's super super good, wait, I got a super good one!
え、最高じゃんかみんな!
Eh, you guys are the best!
ナイス!
Nice!
お水。よし、一息つこう。
Water. Alright, let's take a breath.
えーさてさて、じゃあねね、次のね、楽曲の説明しちゃおうかな、そろそろ。
Eh well then, shall Nene explain the next song soon?
あ、いいよ。まだ撮ってていいからね。この感じで説明しよっか、次の曲まで。
Ah, it's fine. You can still take pictures. Let's explain in this pose until the next song.
どれがいいのかな? ああ、これで説明するわ、じゃあ。
Which one is good? Ah, I'll explain with this, then.
え、次の曲はですね、あの、みんなからすごくリクエストが多かったんですけど、
Eh, the next song is one that had a lot of requests from everyone,
あの、なかなかね、あの歌枠とかでは歌わずに、今までずっと撮っておいた曲をね、披露していきたいと思うんですよ、みんなさ。
but it's a song we haven't sung in song streams, and have kept saved up until now, so I want to showcase it, everyone.
そう、披露していきたいと思うんです。
Yes, I want to showcase it.
この曲もね、踊りの振り付けがついておりますので、よかったらみんなさん、え、ご照覧ください?
This song also has choreography to it, so if you'd like, everyone, please witness it?
なんか、いい感じに見てもらうのってなんて言うんだっけな? みんなさん、ご照覧ください、よろしくお願いします。
What is it called when you have people look at it nicely? Everyone, please witness it, thank you very much.
というわけで、次の曲に行ってみましょう! それでは聞いてください!
And with that, let's head to the next song! Now then, please listen!
好きになって！もっと！
Fall in love with me more!
私を見て！もっと！
Look at me more!
恩返しは“愛のこもった投げキッスで”
My repayment is a kiss blown with love!
愛のこもった投げキッスで
...a kiss blown with love!
気のせいじゃない 目は合ってるよ
It's not your imagination, our eyes are meeting.
ハート作って 恋しちゃってください！
Make a heart and fall in love with me!
やれること 何でもします
I'll do whatever it takes.
NG無しで 体当たり挑戦
No holds barred, taking on any challenge.
エゴサで見つけた アンチのコメ
The anti comments I found from ego-surfing...
ふざけんな！…誰より分かってるし
Are you kidding me?! ...I know that better than anyone.
でも大丈夫 ステージに立てばみんながいる
But it's alright, when I stand on stage, everyone is here.
いくよ！
Let's go!
好きになって！もっと！
Fall in love with me more!
私を見て！もっと！
Look at me more!
恩返しは“愛のこもった投げキッスで”
My repayment is a kiss blown with love!
好きになって！もっと！
Fall in love with me more!
私を見て！もっと！
Look at me more!
恩返しは“愛のこもった投げキッスで”
My repayment is a kiss blown with love!
虜にする！もっと！夢を見せる！もっと！
I'll captivate you more! I'll show you more dreams!
楽しんでって 愛のこもったスペシャルナイト
Enjoy yourselves in this special night full of love.
ファンサしちゃうぞ
I'll give you fan service!
お手紙も 書いてください！
Please write letters to me too!
何度も読んで 宝物にします
I'll read them over and over and make them my treasure.
スキャンダル まだ早いけど
A scandal is still too early,
裏切りません！ 宣言しときます
But I promise I won't betray you!
嫉妬、嫌がらせには 負けない
I won't lose to jealousy or harassment.
ふざけんな！ 実力で勝ってやる
Are you kidding me?! I'll win with pure skill.
だから 辞めない 負けず嫌い 私は いる
That's why I won't quit, as a sore loser who is here.
いくよ！
Let's go!
こぶし突き上げて！もっと！
Raise your fists up more!
汗をかいて！もっと！
Sweat more!
恩返しは“愛のこもったmonaビームで”
My repayment is with a loving mona beam!
大歓声！もっと！まだまだね！ねぇ！もっと！
Loud cheers! More! Still more! Hey, more!
受け止めてね 愛のこもった わがままソング
Accept this selfish song filled with love.
ファンサしちゃうぞ
I'll give you fan service!
はぁ… 終わりが 近づく 寂しい ね
Ah... the ending is approaching, how lonely.
楽しい のに 泣き そう だよ
Even though it's fun, I feel like crying.
次 も 次 も また 会える よね ？
We'll meet again and again, right?
優しさ に 溢れ ている 言葉 も
Words overflowing with kindness,
心 ない 誰か の 言葉 さえも
Even the heartless words of someone,
必要 なんだ 必要 なんだ
Are necessary, are necessary,
強く なろう
I will grow stronger.
好きに叫べ！もっと！
Shout out freely more!
楽しんじゃえ！もっと！
Enjoy yourselves more!
忘れないで 特別な日 になりますように
Don't forget, so that this becomes a special day.
共に歌おう ずっと！ 共に歩もう ずっと！
Let's sing together forever! Let's walk together forever!
合言葉は とびっきりの L・O・V・E
Our watchword is a stunning L-O-V-E!
好きになって！もっと！
Fall in love with me more!
私を見て！もっと！
Look at me more!
恩返しは“愛のこもった投げキッスで”
My repayment is a kiss blown with love!
虜にする！もっと！夢を見せる！もっと！
I'll captivate you more! I'll show you more dreams!
楽しんでって 愛のこもったスペシャルナイト
Enjoy yourselves in this special night full of love.
ファンサしちゃうぞ
I'll give you fan service!
ありがとうございました！ファンサをお聞きいただきました！
Thank you very much! You've just heard 'Fansa'!
え、みんなどうだったでしょうか？BGMください！
So, how was it everyone? Please give me some BGM!
あー水！おいしー！
Ah, water! So good!
さてさて、もうね、8時50分を迎えようとしております皆様！
Now then, it's about to be 8:50 PM, everyone!
今日ね、ここここためにね、ねねはずっと踊りとね、踊りながら歌うっていうことをね、練習してきたんだけど、その成果がみんなに出せたね、しようか。どうだったかな？どう？
Today, Nene has been practicing dancing and singing at the same time for this very moment... I wonder if I was able to show everyone the results. How was it? How?
と、と...
Wait, wait...
あっすごいくるくるだった
Ah, that was super dizzy!
あっすごいよかった
Ah, that was so great!
うわあ！
Whoa!
よかったかい？よかった！
Was it good? It was good!
頑張ったかいがあったみんな、ありがとね！
All your support paid off, thank you everyone!
ていうわけでこっからね、ネネから2大お知らせというか、重大発表というかがありまーす！
So from here, Nene has two announcements, or rather, major announcements!
ていうわけで、1つめの重大発表、だーい！
And so, the first major announcement, ta-da!
ももすずねね 3D化記念グッズ、4月18日販売開始！
Momosuzu Nene 3D Anniversary Goods on sale April 18th!
はい、というわけで3Dのアクリルスタンドと
Yes, so we have the 3D acrylic stand,
ネッコのねラバーストラップと
and Nekko's rubber strap,
あとねネネがいつも着てるウエアの、あの無駄元についてるワッペンバッチが出ます。
and a patch on the collar of the outfit Nene always wears.
ていうわけで詳細を見ていきたいと思います。
So let's take a look at the details.
こういう感じ！めっちゃいい感じにしよ。すごいね。
Like this! It turned out super nice. Amazing.
可愛いこう写真に撮ってもらえたんだ。
You can take cute photos with it.
このね台座も見てよ、この立ってるやつ。これすごい可愛くない？
And look at this base, the standing piece. Isn't this super cute?
あのね、もうね、ごめんなさい、みんなのがあるから、その隣にね、
Since everyone's are already out, right next to them—
その隣にぜひ置いてもらって、なんならもう歴代先輩のみんなのあるからさ、
please put it right next to them, since all the successive senpais' are there too—
その隣に置いてもらって、よろしくお願いします！
please put it next to them, I'd really appreciate it!
ネッコのラバーストラップと、ハーンのね、ワッペンバッチなんだけど
And we have Nekko's rubber strap and the "HAAAN" patch,
みんな見て、ネッコのラバーストラップね、ネネが描いたやつそのままラバーストラップにしてもらいました。
everyone look, Nekko's rubber strap is made directly from the drawing Nene drew.
めっちゃ可愛い！
It's super cute!
もうめちゃめちゃ可愛い。みて、裏面にはネネのサインが入ってんだよみんな。すごくない？
Super cute. Look, on the back it has Nene's signature, everyone. Isn't that amazing?
そしてね、ハーンのワッペンバッチなんだけど、これ見本の画像だからね、ちょっと質感とかあれなんだけど、本当にめっちゃ布って感じ！
And the "HAAAN" patch—this is a sample image so the texture might differ, but it really feels just like fabric!
めっちゃヌノって感じでね、裏面にバッチがついてて、
Super fabric-like, with a badge on the back,
動きに合わせてパーカー出してんだよねみんな、
You guys wear hoodies with your movement,
だからそのパーカーにこうやってペロッって貼るのどうだよみんな、ネネはお勧め！
so how about slapping it right onto your hoodie? Nene recommends that!
はい、このグッズなんですけど
So as for these goods,
この後、21時からね、販売開始になりますので
sales will start after this at 21:00,
たぶん今ね、概要欄が更新されたと思うので、よかったらみんなそっからねリンク、びゅって飛んでもらって
so I think the description box has been updated, please feel free to fly over via the link there,
あの、どう？みんなおねがい。おねがい、おおきい！ネネが喜ぶからみんなおねがい、おねがいおねがいっていうわけでね、よかったらチェックしてください。よろしくお願いします。
so how is it everyone? Please. Please, big! Nene will be happy so please everyone, please please—so please check it out. Thank you.
そしてもう1個の重大発表、みんななんだと思うかねみんな？なんだと思う？なんだと思う？
And what do you guys think the other major announcement is? What do you think?
はい、こちら！ももすずねね2ndシングル『Lunch with me』が、4月19日0:00から配信開始になります！イエーイ！
Yes, here! Momosuzu Nene's 2nd single "Lunch with me" will be available starting April 19th at 0:00! Yay!
え、これね、なんと1曲目に続いて、ヒゲドライバーさんにまたお願いをしました。ありがとうございます！
And you know, following the first song, we asked Higedriver-san again. Thank you very much!
えっとね、最近ね、忙しくてなかなかできなかったあの、お昼はっく？うん、それに関する曲になってます。
Well, recently I've been busy and haven't been able to do lunch talks as much... so it's a song related to that.
ね、今回もネネがちゃんとジャケットを描いているので、よかったらねチェックよろしくお願いします！
And this time too, Nene drew the jacket illustration properly, so please check it out!
さて、『Lunch with me』いったいどんな曲なんだろうか？気になるんじゃないじゃろか？
Now, what kind of song is "Lunch with me" anyway? Aren't you curious?
というわけで今日はみんなに生歌で初披露しようと思ったんですけど、
So today, Nene wanted to debut it live for everyone here,
この曲ができ立てほやほやすぎて生歌を練習する時間がなくて、
but the song is so brand new that there wasn't time to practice singing it live...
でもせっかくならみんなにいいものを聴いてもらおうとネネはひらめいた。
but wanting everyone to hear something great, Nene had an idea.
完成音源を聴いてもらおうと思って。振り付けもまだないので、
To have you listen to the finished audio. Since there's no choreography yet,
ネネが可愛いと思った動きをしながら聴いてもらいたいと思います。
Nene will do movements she thinks are cute while you listen.
今日は長い間見てくれてありがとうございました。なんと世界の、
Thank you so much for watching for a long time today. And amazingly,
世界トレンドランキング1位も！ありがとうございますみんな本当にありがとう！
even world trend ranking #1! Thank you everyone, thank you so much!
今日のためにいろんなことを頑張ってきたからね、ありがとう。
I've worked hard on so many things for today, thank you.
この曲がラストになりますが、3Dになれたネネはこれからも頑張ってい...
This will be our final song, but Nene will keep doing her best in 3D...
今まで頑張りたいと思っておりますので、これからも応援もよろしくお願いします。
I've been doing my best so far, so I'd appreciate your continued support from now on too.
えー直前に遊びに来てくれたラミィも、
Um, thank you to Lamy who came to visit right before,
ディスコードくれたみんなも、Twitterで反応してくれた先輩たちも、本当に本当にありがとうございました。
everyone on Discord, and the seniors who reacted on Twitter, thank you so much, really.
僕にも来てくれてありがとうございました。
Thank you so much for coming to see me too.
えー本当に最高の日になってよかった。
Ah, I'm so glad it turned into the best day.
大雨警報だったら死ぬんだけど、もっぺこぺがりに晴れたし、
If there was a heavy rain warning I'd have died, but it cleared up completely,
本当に今日は最高の日でした。みんな本当にありがと。
and today really was the best day. Thank you all so much.
これからもねねのことよろしくお願いします！
Please keep supporting Nene from now on too!
というわけで、最後の曲、聞いてください！
And with that, please listen to our final song!
えー「ランチタイムミー」なんですけど、
Um, it's called "Lunch with me",
ちょっとごめんね、間違えちゃったのMCをいま。
but sorry, I just messed up the MC.
あのね、あの、ここ夜じゃんか？
You see, um, it's nighttime right here, right?
夜でランチタイムミーってなんかちょっとあれじゃない？
Saying "Lunch with me" at night is a bit... you know?
だからさ、今からねねの力でさ、昼間に戻すからさ、昼のステージね、ね、やっていい？
So right now, using Nene's power, I'm going to turn it back to daytime, so let's do the daytime stage, okay?
お昼に、まーたーねー！
Returning to daytime! See you later!
昼、昼に戻ってきたので、本当に最後の最後に、
Since we've returned to daytime, for the very, very last one,
聞いてください！「ランチタイムミー！」
please listen! "Lunch with me!"
遅く起きた朝はなんだかいつもより眠くて
Waking up late this morning makes me feel sleepier than usual.
昨日の夜ずっとマンガを読んでから眠れなくなってた
Staying up all night reading manga yesterday made me unable to sleep.
今頃そっちはどこで何をしているかななんて
Wondering what you might be doing somewhere right about now
考えてたら心がふっと軽くなるんだ
makes my heart suddenly feel so light.
これは内緒なんだけど昨日読んだマンガの
This is a secret, but the protagonist of the manga I read yesterday...
主人公に君がちょっと似ていたんだよ
you looked a little bit like him.
ねぇ お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 一緒に お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 食べようよ
Hey, noon, noon, noon, noon, noon, noon, let's have lunch together, noon, noon, noon, noon, noon, noon, let's eat!
ちょっとだけ同じ気持ち共有したくて
I just wanted to share that same feeling for a little bit.
そう お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 だけでも 全然特別なことじゃなくても
Yeah, even if it's just noon, even if it's nothing special at all,
いつもの君でいいんだよ 一緒に食べようよ
you can just be your usual self. Let's eat together!
決してリア充とは言えない地味な日々だけど
Even though these plain days are far from glamorous,
なぜだろう最近は少しキラキラなんだ
for some reason, lately they feel a bit sparkly.
こんなに直前に嫌なことあっても君に会えると思うとニヤけちゃってさ
Even when bad things happen right before, thinking I get to see you makes me grin.
ねぇ お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 一緒に お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 食べようよ
Hey, noon, noon, noon, noon, noon, noon, let's have lunch together, noon, noon, noon, noon, noon, noon, let's eat!
ひとりよりきっと楽しくなるから
Because everything's bound to be more fun than being alone.
そう お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 だけだし全然特別なことじゃなくても
Yeah, even if it's just noon, and even if it's nothing special at all,
変なこと考えないでよ まぁ別にいいけど
don't think anything weird about it... well, I guess it's fine either way.
知ってるかな 君がくれることは一つ一つ
Did you know? Every single thing you give me—
うれしくなったり楽しかったり不思議なパワーを感じるってこと
whether it makes me happy or joyful—gives me this mysterious power.
ねぇ お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 一緒に お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 食べようよ
Hey, noon, noon, noon, noon, noon, noon, let's have lunch together, noon, noon, noon, noon, noon, noon, let's eat!
ちょっとだけ同じ気持ち共有したくて
I just wanted to share that same feeling for a little bit.
そう お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 だけでもいつでも君がいいんだよ 一緒に食べようよ
Yeah, even if it's just noon, I always want it to be you. Let's eat together!
言葉は一つ一つ
Every single word—
うれしくなったり楽しかったり不思議なパワーを感じるってこと
whether it makes me happy or joyful—gives me this mysterious power.
ねぇ お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 一緒に お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 食べようよ
Hey, noon, noon, noon, noon, noon, noon, let's have lunch together, noon, noon, noon, noon, noon, noon, let's eat!
ちょっとだけ同じ気持ち共有したくて
I just wanted to share that same feeling for a little bit.
そう お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 だけでもいつでも君がいいんだよ 一緒に食べようよ
Yeah, even if it's just noon, I always want it to be you. Let's eat together!
遥々起きた 朝は なんだか いつもより眠くて
Waking up far away this morning, somehow I'm sleepier than usual,
昨日の夜ずっとマンガを読んでたら眠れなくなってさ
I stayed up reading manga all last night, so I couldn't fall asleep.
今頃そっちはどこで何をしてるかななんて
Wondering what you're up to and where you are right now,
考えてたら心がふわりと軽くなるんだ
Thinking about it makes my heart feel light and airy.
これは内緒なんだけど昨日読んだマンガの
This is a secret, but the protagonist of the manga I read yesterday...
主人公に君がちょっと似てたんだよ
...kind of looked a little bit like you!
ねぇ お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 一緒に
Hey, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, let's have lunch together—
お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 お昼 食べよう
Lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, lunch, let's eat together!
ちょっとだけ同じ気持ち共有したくて
Just wanting to share the exact same feeling for a bit,
そうお昼お昼お昼お昼お昼お昼だけでも
Yeah, even if it's just for lunchtime,
全然特別なことじゃなくてさ
It's nothing special at all, but...
桃鈴ねね 3Dお披露目
[Momosuzu Nene 3D Debut]